<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<Timeline>
   <LockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_locked.ddx</LockedImage>

   <Event>
      <Name>TheDocks01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>1.0</Position>
      <Title>Ngày 16 tháng 1 năm 2498</Title>
      <Date>Ngày 16 tháng 1 năm 2498</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Thuộc địa Arcadia đã xây dựng DSRA, viết tắt của Deep Space Research Array (Viện Nghiên cứu Không gian Sâu) để nghiên cứu các hiện tượng như lỗ đen và các khu vực ngoài tầm với của tàu thamw dò. Nhưng rồi DSRA đã bị phá hủy vì cuộc xâm lược Arcadia của Covenant vào năm 2531.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Event001</Name>
      <Status>Unlocked</Status>
      <Position>5.0</Position>
      <Title>Năm 2506</Title>
      <Date>Năm 2506</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Dự án ORION, nó là dự án nguyên mẫu về SPARTAN - một dự án trong đó cả Chính phủ Quân sự (Colonial Military Administration) cố gắng thành lập một đội siêu chiến binh để thực hiện các hoạt động quân sự bí mật ở Outer Colonies. Mặc dù những Spartan này đạt được một số thành công, nhưng sức mạnh của họ không đáp ứng được kỳ vọng ban đầu, đồng thời chi phí phát triển và thực hiện quá lớn đến mức dự án phải bị hủy bỏ. Những người lính trong dự án này sau đó đã được chuyển đến đội quân đặc biệt khác.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Event002</Name>
      <Status>Unlocked</Status>
      <Position>14.0</Position>
      <Title>Ngày 17 tháng 8 năm 2517</Title>
      <Date>Ngày 17 tháng 8 năm 2517</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Tiến sĩ Catherine Halsey và trung úy của cô, Jacob Keyes, bí mật sàng lọc các đối tượng thử nghiệm đầu tiên dành cho dự án "SPARTAN-II". Họ kết luận rằng, trong số các ứng cử viên - một nhóc có tên là "John" - là đối tượng lý tưởng nhất cho dự án. Sau đó Tiến sĩ Halsey quyết định đưa nhóc nhập ngũ một cách bí mật.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Event003</Name>
      <Status>Unlocked</Status>
      <Position>15.0</Position>
      <Title>Ngày 23 tháng 9 năm 2517</Title>
      <Date>Ngày 23 tháng 9 năm 2517</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Dự án SPARTAN-II của Tiến sĩ Halsey đã bắt đầu trên hành tinh Reach của hệ sao Epsilon Eridani. 75 chàng trai và cô gái đã trải qua quá trình huấn luyện nghiêm ngặt về thể chất và tinh thần, sau đó họ được đưa vào chương trình tăng cường xương và cơ bắp.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BlackBox04</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>18.0</Position>
      <Title>Ngày 20 tháng 7 năm 2520</Title>
      <Date>Ngày 20 tháng 7 năm 2520</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Alexander, dân quân với chức thuyền trưởng cuối cùng của tàu Spirit of Fire, anh ấy đã nghỉ hưu sau khi hoàn thành nhiệm vụ ở Verent. UNSC sau đó đã trưng dụng con tàu và biến nó thành tàu chiến.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_blackbox.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BlackBox05</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>20.0</Position>
      <Title>Ngày 1 tháng 9 năm 2520</Title>
      <Date>Ngày 1 tháng 9 năm 2520</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Lực lượng của tàu Spirit of Fire đã hoàn thành việc tu sửa lớn tại xưởng đóng tàu trên quỹ đạo hành tinh Reach và sẽ bắt đầu sứ mệnh của mình với tư cách là tàu hỗ trợ mặt đất, bắt đầu với Chiến dịch TREBUCHET.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_blackbox.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>PirthOutskirts01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>22.0</Position>
      <Title>Sắc lệnh tối cao của Prophet of Restraint</Title>
      <Date>Năm 2524</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Con tàu của Kig-Yar: "Pitiless" đã đưa xác của một người đàn ông ô uế lên con tàu. Hãy nghe đây: Ta phải tìm toàn bộ những con tàu của Kig-Yar. Hãy để Sangheili trung thành dẫn đầu Unggoy và lục soát mọi con tàu của Kig-Yar để tìm thêm bằng chứng về những kẻ ô uế như người đàn ông đó. Hãy thực hiện điều này NGAY BÂY GIỜ.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_covenant.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BlackBox11</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>23.0</Position>
      <Title>Sắc lệnh tối cao của Prophet of Tolerance</Title>
      <Date>Năm 2524</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Hãy nghe đây: Hơn 500 đội được giao nhiệm vụ nghiên cứu ngôn ngữ của những kẻ ô uế. Mỗi đội phải gồm có Unggoy và Sangheili đủ thông minh. Họ sẽ chỉ nói chuyện với nhau bằng ngôn ngữ của những kẻ ô uế. Nếu toàn bộ lực lượng tấn công của chúng ta học được ngôn ngữ của những kẻ ô uế, chúng sẽ rơi vào tình trạng bối rối.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_blackbox.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Prophet02</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>26.0</Position>
      <Title>Trích từ Punished Deeds (Quả Báo), Tập III</Title>
      <Date>Năm 2525</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Regret trở thành linh mục cao cấp ở độ tuổi trẻ thông qua việc thao túng dư luận và tống tiền những người xung quanh hắn. Một số Prophet, bao gồm cả Regret, đã gặp được Oracle, một trí tuệ nhân tạo (AI) cổ xưa, nơi mà hắn biết được rằng con người bằng cách nào đó có mối liên hệ với chủng tộc Forerunner và hắn cũng biết được điều gì đó có thể làm lung lay nền tảng đức tin của Covenant. Quyết định tiêu diệt loài người của họ nhằm che giấu những sự thật này vẫn còn gây tranh cãi cho đến ngày nay.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_covenant.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>
   <Event>
      <Name>Chasms01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>27.0</Position>
      <Title>Sắc lệnh tối cao của Prophet of Truth</Title>
      <Date>Năm 2525</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Toàn bộ anh em Covenant hãy nghe và làm theo mệnh lệnh đây. Tất cả bộ binh và tàu chiến đều phải tấn công những hành tinh có con người ở trong hệ sao Epsilon Indi. Tập trung sử dụng toàn bộ hỏa lực. Thực hiện mệnh lệnh thật nghiêm khắc và không để lại bất cứ con người nào sống sót phía sau.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_covenant.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Event004</Name>
      <Status>Unlocked</Status>
      <Position>28.0</Position>
      <Title>Ngày 3 Tháng 2 năm 2525</Title>
      <Date>Ngày 3 Tháng 2 năm 2525</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Liên lạc với thuộc địa nông nghiệp Harvest đã bị ngắt. Khi những nỗ lực để kết nối lại với họ đều thất bại, nỗi sợ hãi về điều tồi tệ nhất bắt đầu xuất hiện. Trong khi đó, tại Office of Naval Intelligence (Cơ quan Tình báo Hải quân) gần hành tinh Reach đang có cuộc phẫu thuật tăng cường sức mạnh cho các ứng cử viên của dự án SPARTAN-II. Trong quá trình này, nhiều ứng viên sẽ chết hoặc bị thương tật.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Arbiter01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>29.0</Position>
      <Title>Trích từ Punished Deeds (Quả Báo), Tập III</Title>
      <Date>Năm 2525</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Tên Arbiter mới được bổ nhiệm này không hề sợ chết, nhưng lại sợ đi vào di tích cổ. Trước khi vào khu di tích, hắn đã cử một đội Unggoy đến kiểm tra xem nó có an toàn không. Nếu an toàn, họ sẽ sống sót, nhưng nếu phát hiện cảm giác nguy hiểm dù là nhỏ nhất, tên Arbiter sẽ cho nổ quả bom plasma được gắn trên bình methan của Unggoy.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_covenant.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Event005</Name>
      <Status>Unlocked</Status>
      <Position>30.0</Position>
      <Title>Ngày 20 tháng 4 năm 2525</Title>
      <Date>Ngày 20 tháng 4 năm 2525</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Liên lạc với tàu trinh sát Argo đã bị mất, nó là chiếc tàu được cử đến để điều tra sự cố trên Harvest. Để xử lý vấn đề này, một hạm đội vũ trang lớn đang được tập hợp.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Arbiter02</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>31.0</Position>
      <Title>Trích từ Punished Deeds (Quả Báo), Tập III</Title>
      <Date>Năm 2525</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Tên Arbiter mới được bổ nhiệm ngay lập tức được đưa vào thử thách. Có một căn cứ không gian khổng lồ của những Người Cổ Đại đang ở gần tàn tích bị bỏ hoang, nó được cho là chứa đựng 'chìa khóa' để đánh thức công nghệ cổ đại này. Nhưng căn cứ này đã được bảo vệ nghiêm ngặt bởi một nhóm Elite chống lại các Prophet mới được bổ nhiệm. Tên Arbiter đã đánh bại tất cả bọn họ trong một trận chiến kéo dài vài ngày. Chìa khóa đó vẫn chưa bao giờ được tìm thấy nhưng bằng chứng của cuộc chiến này đã bị giấu kín.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_covenant.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Event006</Name>
      <Status>Unlocked</Status>
      <Position>32.0</Position>
      <Title>Ngày 7 tháng 10 năm 2525</Title>
      <Date>Ngày 7 tháng 10 năm 2525</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Phi đội D đã tới Harvest và giao chiến với Covenant, nhưng họ buộc phải nhảy không gian để quay trở về Reach sau khi hai trong số ba con tàu của họ bị phá hủy bởi tàu chiến của Covenant. Trong công cuộc chiến đấu, họ đã nhận được tin nhắn thoại đến từ Covenant, nội dung của tin nhắn là: "Sự tuyệt diệt của các ngươi là ý chí của những vị thần... và ta là công cụ của họ."  Vì tin nhắn này được gửi bằng tiếng Anh, nó cho chúng ta thấy rằng Covenant đã nghiên cứu về loài người được một thời gian.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>FrozenValley01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>33.0</Position>
      <Title>Ngày 1 tháng 11 năm 2525</Title>
      <Date>Ngày 1 tháng 11 năm 2525</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Quân đội UNSC đang hoàn toàn cảnh giác cao độ và bắt đầu chuẩn bị cho một cuộc tấn công nhằm chiếm lại Harvest. Đồng thời tất cả các đơn vị chiến đấu của Chính phủ Quân sự (Colonial Military Administration) ngay lập tức được kiểm soát dưới mệnh lệnh của Bộ Tư lệnh Hải quân/Bộ Tư lệnh Lực lượng Mặt đất "trong suốt tình huống khủng hoảng". Dự án SPARTAN-II đã được đẩy nhanh đến giai đoạn cuối: MJOLNIR, một bộ giáp mới được dành riêng cho Spartan.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Tundra01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>34.0</Position>
      <Title>Ngày 27 tháng 11 năm 2525</Title>
      <Date>Ngày 27 tháng 11 năm 2525</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Toàn bộ lính SPARTAN-II đều được đưa đến Cơ sở Thử nghiệm Vật liệu Damascus tại thuộc địa Chi Ceti-4 để được trang bị bộ giáp MJOLNIR. Họ chỉ có vài giờ để kiểm tra bộ giáp trước khi tàu của người ngoài hành tinh xâm nhập vào hệ thống và tấn công tàu hỗ trợ đang bay quanh quỹ đạo của họ. Trong trận chiến này, có ba Spartan đã xâm nhập vào tàu địch, giao chiến với binh lính của Covenant và chiếm giữ được chiếc khiên năng lượng của kẻ thù. Nhưng có một Spartan đã thiệt mạng trong trận chiến này.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Prophet01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>35.0</Position>
      <Title>Sắc lệnh tối cao của Prophet of Regret</Title>
      <Date>Năm 2525</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Nghe đây, tin xấu đã đến từ hệ hành tinh Chi Ceti. Do sự thiếu niềm tin đến từ một số nhân sự của con tàu Unrelenting, một nhóm của những Kẻ Ô Uế đã xâm nhập và thực hiện các vụ thảm sát. Ta ra lệnh thành lập Phòng Khoa học để tiến hành nghiên cứu kỹ lưỡng về vũ khí và bộ giáp mà chúng ta lấy được từ chúng.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_covenant.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Event007</Name>
      <Status>Unlocked</Status>
      <Position>36.0</Position>
      <Title>Trận Chiến tại Harvest, năm 2526</Title>
      <Date>Năm 2526</Date>
      <DetailText>
         At the Battle of Harvest, Vice Admiral Preston Cole's war fleet - one of the largest ever mobilized - engages the alien warship responsible for the decimation of the colony, scoring a victory. Only Cole's last-minute tactical inspiration turns the tide of battle. Upon his return to Earth, Cole is promoted to the rank of Admiral.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>TerminalMoraine01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>37.0</Position>
      <Title>Edict of the Office of the High Prophet of Regret</Title>
      <Date>2526</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Let the Victory of Episilon Indi be celebrated by fasting and prayer. Unggoy and Kig-Yar food rations to be eliminated for the next three work periods. Sangheili and Jiralhanae to spend two rest periods in public prayer. All attend the public monitors at the sounding of five bells to observe the execution of those who failed their duty at the Victory.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_covenant.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Cutter01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>39.0</Position>
      <Title>30 January 2528</Title>
      <Date>30 January 2528</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Captain Cutter turns down a command position on board the destroyer class ship The Prophecy. His decision to stay close to his family prompted an ONI psychological examination that determined that while fit to command, his family ties worked against any larger military career.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Brute01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>40.0</Position>
      <Title>Incident Report 16-196901</Title>
      <Date>2528</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Security team called to Jiralhanae Chieftan's quarters at third bell, second shift. Team arrived at location to find quarters door torn from its frame and five chunks of unidentified biological matter in hallway (see attached diagram). Upon inspection, biological matter confirmed as parts of two Unggoy from Deck Four Kitchens. Chieftan was calm and responsive; stated that delivery of his midday meal was not to specifications (thorn beast overdone, dipping sauce insufficient). Maintenance crew notified; official reprimand of D4 Kitchen supervisor filed.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_covenant.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Forge01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>42.0</Position>
      <Title>17 August 2530</Title>
      <Date>17 August 2530</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Sergeant Forge incarcerated for assaulting a senior officer. His career would have been over if Admiral Cole had not intervened and seen that the investigation was fair and above board. The senior officer eventually faced a court martial and Sergeant Forge was assigned to Spirit of Fire in an effort to keep the prior events quiet.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Anders01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>43.0</Position>
      <Title>Professor Anders' Log, 30 January 2531</Title>
      <Date>30 January 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Upon boarding The Last Gleaming, I was shown my quarters. On the door it read "Doctor Anders" - the name my mother wanted me to use in my professional career. I cannot abide being reminded of her wishes. This whole cloak-and-dagger trip has her fingerprints all over it.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BlackBox03</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>44.0</Position>
      <Title>From the Office of the High Prophet of Regret</Title>
      <Date>2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Return at fastest possible speed to the world they know as Harvest. We must learn the secrets inside the holy relic before the Great Journey can continue. The humans must not be allowed to enter the artifact; we will do whatever we must to deny them access. All must be resolute in this task, or face punishment.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_blackbox.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BlackBox01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>45.0</Position>
      <Title>4 February 2531</Title>
      <Date>4 February 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         The UNSC support ship Spirit of Fire enters orbit around Harvest. While Admiral Cole's fleet is engaged elsewhere, Spirit is sent to Harvest to investigate ongoing Covenant activity in the system and look for survivors from the missing UNSC Destroyer The Prophecy (previously dispatched to Harvest to investigate the same activity). Commanded by Captain Cutter, Spirit has been reassigned by FLEETCOM. ONI has placed Professor Anders onboard to lead the investigation.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_blackbox.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BlackBox09</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>46.0</Position>
      <Title>6 February 2531</Title>
      <Date>6 February 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Professor Anders writes her father what appears to be a detailed analysis of Homer's Odyssey. In fact it is a coded message detailing her mission to Harvest and the result of the find there. ONI censors miss the cipher completely and the message passes unaltered to her father.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_blackbox.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BlackBox02</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>48.0</Position>
      <Title>7 February 2531</Title>
      <Date>7 February 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Spirit of Fire holds service for the crew of the Prophecy. The crew roster is read despite objections from ONI personnel. The Prophecy was lost with all hands on a first expedition to Harvest to investigate the Covenant interest in the artifact found near the polar region.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_blackbox.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>
   
   <Event>
      <Name>BlackBox07</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>49.0</Position>
      <Title>9 February 2531</Title>
      <Date>9 February 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         After engaging Covenant forces on the surface of Harvest, the UNSC vessel Spirit of Fire arrives at Arcadia - only to find that the Covenant are already there and attacking the colony. Spirit's ground forces assist in the evacuation, and help fight the Covenant to a standstill on the surface of the planet.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_blackbox.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BlackBox06</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>50.0</Position>
      <Title>From the Office of the High Prophet of Regret</Title>
      <Date>2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Arbiter, you are the Hand of the Covenant - my hand. You know what must be done. Return to the surface and capture the human female - the one who managed to make fools of us on Harvest. She is the key to unlocking the secrets of the Ancients.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_blackbox.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BlackBox08</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>51.0</Position>
      <Title>10 February 2531</Title>
      <Date>10 February 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         The capture of Professor Anders forces Captain Cutter's hand; Spirit of Fire pursues the enemy into Covenant space. The ship's AI projects an arrival at their destination in 312 hours. The ship remains on high alert for the duration, though nonessential crewmembers are briefly placed in cryo sleep.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_blackbox.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Forge02</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>52.0</Position>
      <Title>11 February 2531</Title>
      <Date>11 February 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Sergeant Forge confronts SPARTAN Douglas-042 over his recommendation to destroy the Covenant ship carrying Professor Anders. The altercation results in a broken chair, a seal malfunction on a bulkhead door and a stern interruption by the ship's AI, Serina. 42 and Forge always eat together in the mess hall following this event.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BlackBox10</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>54.0</Position>
      <Title>14 February 2531</Title>
      <Date>14 February 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Serina, knowing that the crew may be on a one way trip, manufactures and delivers fake emails from family members to the crew celebrating Valentine's Day. She uses previous correspondence as a basis for the letters. No one ever suspects her of this deception.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_blackbox.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BlackBox12</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>56.0</Position>
      <Title>Trích từ Punished Deeds (Quả Báo), Tập III</Title>
      <Date>2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         The shield world that Regret intended to activate was one of just a few that the Covenant had uncovered in the quest for the Halos. These treasure chests of technology enabled the Covenant to quickly gain access to advanced weaponry and space propulsion systems allowing them to dominate the galaxy.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_blackbox.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BlackBox13</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>57.0</Position>
      <Title>23 February 2531</Title>
      <Date>23 February 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Spirit of Fire arrives at an uncharted planet swarming with strange alien lifeforms. Within a day, the ship is drawn into the planet's interior, where the crew confronts the Covenant and eventually rescues Professor Anders.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_blackbox.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Exile01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>58.0</Position>
      <Title>Cutter's Log, 25 February 2531</Title>
      <Date>25 February 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Pelicans engaged in ground operations on the outside of the shell planet failed invariably within four to five flights. The dust adhered to the intakes during entry into the planetary atmosphere in an almost defensive manner, as if the planet itself did not want any space vehicles descending down to its surface.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BlackBox15</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>59.0</Position>
      <Title>25 February 2531</Title>
      <Date>25 February 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Thanks to Sergeant Forge's sacrifice, Spirit of Fire escapes from the Forerunner shield world. Spirit of Fire sets a course for home as the majority of the crew prepare to enter cryo sleep for a journey that will take years, if not decades.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_blackbox.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Release01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>60.0</Position>
      <Title>Chief Medical Officer O'Neil's Log, 26 February 2531</Title>
      <Date>26 February 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         The decision to burn bodies infected with the virus was not taken lightly, but the danger to the crew, and the sheer voracity of the infection made taking the bodies aboard Spirit of Fire impossible. Study of the virus and its effects also seems unwise given that we are not equipped with any quarantine labs or have the faintest idea how the virus spreads.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BlackBox14</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>62.0</Position>
      <Title>1 March 2531</Title>
      <Date>1 March 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Chief Engineer Prescott finishes his assessment of damage to Spirit of Fire and repairs continue to the hull. The FTL core reactor cannot be replaced and plans to manufacture a spare from base reactor units is considered impossible. The decision is made to run the ship on a skeleton crew and place the rest in suspended animation.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_blackbox.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Anders02</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>63.0</Position>
      <Title>Cutter's Log, 3 March 2531</Title>
      <Date>3 March 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Professor Anders' captivity by the Covenant has made her the longest known POW in the war so far. She has not sought counseling or talked much about her time in captivity but one can only begin to guess at the nightmares she went through during that terrible time.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Labyrinth01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>64.0</Position>
      <Title>Anders' Log, 4 March 2531</Title>
      <Date>4 March 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         The artificial construction of this "world" was far beyond the Covenant. Indeed, they seemed to be scavenging this technology for their own use and were unable to operate the machinery, either by design or advancement. The fact my hand was required to unlock the device leads me to believe the original builders of the planet may have had some knowledge about humans.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Cutter02</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>68.0</Position>
      <Title>12 March 2531</Title>
      <Date>12 March 2531</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Captain Cutter walks the ship, stepping into medbay to check on the crew still recovering from the battle. He assures Nurse Hershey that a way will be found home and that she will get to see her husband again. He returns to his cabin and after writing five more commendation recommendations, fourteen family condolence letters and a note to his wife, sleeps for the first time in two weeks.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Repository01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>70.0</Position>
      <Title>10 February 2534</Title>
      <Date>10 February 2534</Date>
      <DetailText>
         The UNSC designates Spirit of Fire as "lost with all hands." The previous designation of "missing" had given hope to family and friends. The reason for the change is classified top secret. A memorial service is held for the crew, but many prominent family members do not attend, holding out hope that their loved ones are still alive.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Event008</Name>
      <Status>Unlocked</Status>
      <Position>73.0</Position>
      <Title>1 June 2536</Title>
      <Date>1 June 2536</Date>
      <DetailText>
         The Siege of the Inner Colonies begins as Covenant forces swarm into human-controlled space. For several years, the war falls into a pattern: humans win isolated battles, typically during ground operations, but at horrible cost. One by one, the colonies fall.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BeasleysPlateau01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>84.0</Position>
      <Title>9 September 2549</Title>
      <Date>9 September 2549</Date>
      <DetailText>
         The Second Fall of Arcadia. The Covenant left Arcadia alone after their first attack on the planet in 2531 but the humans mostly abandoned it, leaving the capital city Pirth to nature. Eventually a small rural farming community started Abaskun, a rich farmland area on the continent of Mu. Although mostly lawless, the area provided much needed food supplies to the UNSC until the planet was attacked again by the Covenant in the fall of 2549.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>FortDeen01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>86.0</Position>
      <Title>Edict of the Office of the High Prophet of Truth</Title>
      <Date>2550</Date>
      <DetailText>
         It is known that there is delay installing Luminaries upon newly constructed vessels of war. On each vessel still lacking a Luminary, one Unggoy worker out of every 64 is to be executed. To preserve discipline between the Sangheili overseers and Unggoy, choice of victim and execution is to be by Kig-Yar death squads. This to continue daily until that vessel's Luminary is installed.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_covenant.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>BloodGulch01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>90.0</Position>
      <Title>27 August 2552</Title>
      <Date>27 August 2552</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Twenty-five of the twenty-eight surviving SPARTAN-IIs, including SPARTAN-117, are recalled to Reach to be briefed on the Covenant threat and to receive their new orders: board a damaged Covenant vessel, use a "mission specialist" to crack the Covenant computer system, and locate the Covenant homeworld. Once accomplished, a covert team will be dispatched to capture the Covenant leadership and broker a truce by force. Despite recent successes, the human military is being systematically slaughtered, and this may be the only chance for survival.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Event009</Name>
      <Status>Unlocked</Status>
      <Position>92.0</Position>
      <Title>30 August 2552 - 0400 hours</Title>
      <Date>30 August 2552</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Reach, the home of ONI's CASTLE facility and the Spartan-II project, is attacked by an overwhelming Covenant force. The vessel Pillar of Autumn, Captain Keyes commanding, transports Spartans into battle, hoping to seize a Covenant vessel. Though the Covenant are prevented from learning Earth's location, most of the Spartans fall in battle and Reach is lost.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Event010</Name>
      <Status>Unlocked</Status>
      <Position>93.0</Position>
      <Title>30 August 2552 - 0500 hours</Title>
      <Date>30 August 2552</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Pillar of Autumn, commanded by Captain Keyes, flees Reach with Covenant ships in pursuit. The ship is heavily damaged, but manages to drop into slipspace and escape. Pillar of Autumn carries the only Spartan thought to have survived the engagement on Reach.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_unsc.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Crevice01</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>98.0</Position>
      <Title>Edict of the Office of the High Prophet of Truth</Title>
      <Date>2552</Date>
      <DetailText>
         Hear now all personnel to spend today's second rest period in attentive watchfulness before display monitors. All display monitors to display the humbling and punishment of the Sangheili Supreme Commander of the Fleet of Particular Justice, for failure, cowardice, and lack of faith.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_covenant.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>

   <Event>
      <Name>Brute02</Name>
      <Status>Locked</Status>
      <Position>99.0</Position>
      <Title>Edict of the Office of the High Prophet of Truth</Title>
      <Date>2552</Date>
      <DetailText>
         In recognition of the virtue of the Jiralhanae, it is ordered that all Sangheili aboard the Fleet of Profound Solitude, The Fleet of Tranquil Composure, and the Fleet of Inner Knowledge to be completely replaced by Jiralhanae. Each removed Sangheili to be assigned other duties. In celebration, all imprisoned or criminal Jiralhanae to be released, rehabilitated, and pardoned.
      </DetailText>
      <UnlockedImage>img://art\ui\flash\shared\textures\timeline\timeline_covenant.ddx</UnlockedImage>
   </Event>
</Timeline>
